(Sheldon:)Complete with bulletproof
bracelets and lasso of truth.
(Sheldon:)Invisible plane sold separately.
(Penny:)Wait, why me?
(Penny:)Wh-Why can't your girlfriend
be Wonder Woman?
(Howard:)She and her lab team
are under quarantine.
(Howard:)Seems at the Christmas party
they were doing Jell-O shots
(Howard:)out of petri dishes that used
to contain yellow fever.
(Penny:)Okay, what about
your friend Amy?
(Sheldon:)Amy Farrah Fowler doesn't
believe in wearing costumes.
(Sheldon:)She isn't the free spirit I am.
(Penny:)Okay, well, forget it.
(Penny:)I'm not spending
my New Year's Eve
(Penny:)at a comic book store
wearing a Wonder Woman costume.
(Howard(after Raj whispers to him):)He says he'll wear it
if you'll be Aquaman.
(Leonard:)What are you doing?